(Penny:)Obviously,
I have some commitment issues.
- Glaringly obvious. Go on.
- As long as things keep going great...
(Penny:)...you'll keep asking me to marry you.
Eventually, I'll end up saying yes.
(Penny:)Then we're gonna be married forever
and the whole thing just freaks me out.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Leonard:)I know I propose a lot.
(Leonard:)So how about this?
(Leonard:)I promise I will never ask you
to marry me again.
(Penny:)What do you mean?
Are you breaking up with me?
(Leonard:)No. No, no, no.
(Leonard:)But if someday, you decide
you wanna get married...
(Leonard:)...you have to propose to me.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Leonard:)It's all on you.
But when the time comes,
I want the whole nine yards.
(Leonard:)I want you down on one knee, flowers.
I wanna be swept off my feet.
(Penny:)Yeah, you got it.
(Leonard:)And I'm cool with surprises,
but nothing on a Jumbotron.